IBT0061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Teamster Magazine Story and Photo Files
1980s-2000s
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0061
36 Cubic Feet 36 records center cartons
This collection contains photographs and notes that were used in issues of the International Teamster Magazine.
General
skeletal bib 14561121 MMS ID# 99145611213604107
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
Materials in this collection are loose photographs, notes, and articles that appeared in various issues of the International Teamster Magazine between the 1980s and 2000s. The files are arranged by the date they were slated to appear in the magazine. Many photographs are unlabeled. Photographs include standard photographs, projector slides, contact sheets, and negatives.
Biographical / Historical
Teamsters Magazine is the official magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Photographs are gathered and selected to be shown in each issue of the magazine. Some photographs from issues of Teamsters Magazine are in this collection.
- Advertisements, Series 1
  - Story and Photo Files, Packages Ahold, February 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Ahold Radio, April 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Ahold Song Documents, March 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Farmland Radio Ad, March 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo File, Gary Shoichet letter, June 17 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, NAFTA San Diego Ad, June 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo File, Trucking Bozo Ad, 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, NAFTA Kentucky Ad, May 1996; IBT0061 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Research and Background Files, Series 2
  - Miscellaneous Undated Files (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Undated Files (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, TLA Education Tape, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Education Workshops Taping, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Illustrations, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, General Teamster Video Logs, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, America West Radio Feed, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Black Caucus Video, 1971-1976; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Borg-Warner Radio, Atlanta, 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Capital Police Cards, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Carhaul Radio, 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Convention Press, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, Convention Press - Lists, IBT 0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Flood Relief, 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Free Speech TV, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folders 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, HR2497 - Interview with Prospering in America, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, North American Network, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo Files, NW Air Begins Negotiations, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, Overnite Radio, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pilots Joint Proposal, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Story and Photo File, Stair Cargo Radio, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Story and Photo Files, Stair Cargo Radio #2, 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Story and Photo Files, Studio Budger, 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Story and Photo Files, TV Monitor, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Story and Photo Files, Valujet Vote, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Story and Photo Files, MCLAC, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Medical Advisory Committee Meeting, 1988-1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Medical Advisory Committee Meeting, December 1989; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folders 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Medical Advisory Committee, December 7, 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Newspaper Drivers Annual Meeting, March/April 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Newspaper Drivers - Tampa Tribune, Contact Sheets, May 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, Newspaper Drivers Division, 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Overnite Organizing Meeting - Crystal City, April 3, 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Parcel and Small Package Division, 1988; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO Building and Construction Trade Division Photos, April 1989; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Bakery Conference, 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, 14th Black Caucus, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Canadian Conference, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Cincinnati Rally, September 15, 1987; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Dairy Conference, 1989-1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, DNC Clay Reception, July 17, 1988; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Eastern Conference of Teamsters, Hilton Head, South Carolina, August 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Shea and Durham Meet with Danish Union Reps, November 1989; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, "2 million in 2000" and GEB Meeting - Palm Springs, CA, January 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, GEB, 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo File, GEB 1990, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, GEB Meetings, Montreal Canada, July 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, GEB San Diego, CA, April 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Industrial Trade Meeting, Boston, MA, August 1989; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, Lawyers Conference [Slides], 1987; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Legislative Conference, 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Local Union and Joint Council, 1984; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, Republican National Convention, 1988; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, TMI, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo File, Union Busting, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, Women's March, April 9, 1989; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Appeals, Grievances, Officer's Report and Constitution Original Photos, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Arrangement and Credentials Original Photos, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Officer's Report, May 1986; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Sergeant at Arms Original Photos, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, AFL-CIO, 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo File, American Family Celebration, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Brewery Conference, March 1987 and 1990; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Carhaul Conference, 1988, 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pub EE Complete Copy, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pub EE Working Copy, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pub EE throwaways [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pub EE throwaways [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pub EE throwaways [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Education, 1982; IBT0061 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Freight Convention Photo Files, 1988; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - IBT Staff Slides, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - IBT Staff Story and Photo Files [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - IBT Staff Story and Photo Files [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement, 2-man committee, Chicago, IL, November 1990-March 1991; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, "For Carey, a peak and a valley.", August 24, 1997; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, DNA Radio Ads, 1995; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Ahold, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Amana Background, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Amana Press Clips, 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Amana/Raytheon Press Release, 1996; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Detroit Action Packet, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, Letters of Solidarity [1 of 2], 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Letters of Solidarity [2 of 2], 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Media History, October 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, Media Section New York Times, July 21, 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, Southern Air Transport Media, July 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo Files, Thanks to the Union/UPS, December 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, Background Newspapers, 1996-1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Detroit COJ, July 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Detroit Press Release Pack, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Giles, DNA/Gannett Solidarity, August 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, DNA Master Collection, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, DNA Media, December 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, Continental Press Material, Houston/LA, July 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, Gannett Company, 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, Gannett's Record on Children's Television Programming, August 1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, German Material, April 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, Knight-Riddler Stats, May 1997; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo Files, Nationsbank and Community Reinvestment, August 1995; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, Press Clips, 1994-1996; IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Story and Photo Files, Virginia Media, IBT0061 Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Story and Photo Files, Series 3
  - Story and Photo Files, July/August 1999, June/August 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, April/May 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, July/August 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, October/November 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June/July 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, January/February 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, March/April 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, May/June 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, September/October 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, May/June 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, July/August 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, Photos, Fall 1982; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Election Material, September 1983; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1985, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pictures July 1985 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo File, Pictures July 1985 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1985, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files Pictures, September 1985 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Pictures September 1985 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1985, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1985, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [1 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [2 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [3 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [4 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [5 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [6 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1988 [7 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Photos February 1988 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, Photos February 1988 [2 of 2], Februrary 1988; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [1 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [2 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [3 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [4 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [5 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [6 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 [7 of 7], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1988 Covers, IBT0061 Series 3 (Flat box 18, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1988 [1 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1988 [2 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1988 [3 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1988 [4 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1988 [5 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [1 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [2 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [3 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [4 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [5 of 8], IBT0061 Series (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [6 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [7 of 8], IBT0061 Series (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1988 [8 of 8], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1988 [1 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1988 [2 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1988 [3 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1988 [4 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1988 [5 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1988 [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1988 [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1988 [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1988 [1 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1988 [2 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1988 [3 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1988 [4 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1988 [5 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [1 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [2 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [3 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [4 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [5 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1988 [6 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1989 [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1989 [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1989 [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1989 [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Original Copy May 1989 [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, Original Copy May 1989 [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Original Copy May 1989 [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [1 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [2 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [3 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [4 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [5 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [6 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [7 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [8 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [9 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1989 [10 of 10], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [1 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [2 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [3 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [4 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [5 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1989 [6 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, DRIVE 1990 Photos, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1990, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1990 Photos Not Used, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [1 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [2 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [3 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [4 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [5 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1990 [6 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [1 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [2 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [3 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [4 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [5 of 5], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1990, Photos, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1990 [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1990 [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1990 [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1990 [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1990, Back Up [1 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files September 1990, Back Up [2 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files September 1990, Back Up [3 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1990, Back Up [4 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1990, Back Up [5 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1990, Back Up [6 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1990, Photos, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990 [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990 [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990 [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990 [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990, Photos [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990, Photos [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1990, Photos and Magazine, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Covers, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Photos, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1990, Original and Back Up Copy [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Photos [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 1)